Derek Tu

Los Angeles, CA derektu13@yahoo.com (626) 759-2791

Desire to secure a help desk support position bringing 5 years of customer service experience to ensure that problems encountered by customers are quickly solved. Seeking to work in a fast-paced organization where excellent troubleshooting and multitasking skills will be fully utilized for the growth of the company.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

Work Experience

Help Desk Analyst

California Pizza Kitchen - Los Angeles, CA November 2019 to Present

- Serve as a vital customer service link for IT to restaurants, support center, and service providers
- Document, track, and monitor incident tickets to ensure timely resolutions
- Create, maintain, and disable user accounts and groups, including Active Directory and VPN
- Install, support, and maintain computer desktop, laptop, printers and any related hardware and software, to include asset tracking.
- Support current phone system to include adding, removing and changing phone extensions and creating voicemail accounts
- Create and update knowledge base articles
- Assist in project implementations, testing and documentation

Assistant Store Manager

T-Mobile (HIT Mobile) - Los Angeles, CA August 2018 to November 2019

- Mange a small group of 3 to and train new recruits to meet company standards.
- Troubleshoot mobile devices to support end users such as Android devices, IOS devices, and tablets.
- Ability to learn and teach new technology on any given day.
- Work with virtual client such as Citrix.

Server

Gyu-Kaku Japanese BBQ - Los Angeles, CA April 2017 to August 2018

- Exceptional interpersonal and team building skills with an aptitude for building rapport with a diverse range of clients, managers, and colleagues
- Consistently achieved highest guest check average

Education

Associate in Computer Information Technology

Rio Hondo College

August 2017 to Present

Skills

• Soft Skills: Provide excellent customer service, Great attention to detail, problem solving, time management, adaptability, interpersonal skills,

Computer Skills: Microsoft Office Suite, Computer hardware knowledge, Mobile device OS, IOS, Type 70+ WPM, Knowledge of different OS (Windows 10, Window XP, Vista, 7, Mac OS x)

- Active Directory
- Help Desk
- Desktop Support
- Service Desk
- Technical Support
- Mac OS
- MSP
- VPN